The Rules are Simple: Kill or Be Killed.
Surviving the Game is a action, thriller, adventure
film directed by Ernest R. Dickerson.
A homeless man is hired as a survival guide for a group of wealthy businessmen on a hunting trip in the
mountains, unaware that they are killers who hunt humans for sport, and that he is their new prey.
Burns, played by Rutger Hauer.
Mason, played by Ice-T.
Cole, played by Charles S. Dutton.
Griffin, played by John C. McGinley.
Wolfe, Jr., played by William McNamara.
Hank, played by Jeff Corey.
Surviving the Game is a 1994 American
action-adventure film directed by Ernest R.
Dickerson and written by Eric Bernt.
It is loosely based on the 1924 short story "The Most
Dangerous Game" by Richard Connell.
The film stars Ice-T, Rutger Hauer, Charles S.
Dutton, John C.
McGinley, William McNamara, Gary Busey, and F.
Murray Abraham.
Surviving the Game was released in the United States
on April 15, 1994, by New Line Cinema.
The film received negative reviews from critics and was a box office bomb, grossing $7.7 million against a
production budget of $7.4 million (not including advertisement and distribution costs).
The tone is emotional and intense.